翻译: 约翰 晓小枫 愤豆
*爱*
*Love*
*心相连*
*Connection*
*共经历*
*Experience*
校对: 约翰
赞 Morty
Yeah, Morty.
*一起来*
*Come together*
后期: Nico
*爱 心相连 共经历*
With love, connection, and experience
- 这首歌最喜欢了  - 棒
- It's my favorite song. - Oh, yeah.
压制: 三九度一
失事信标
Oh, yeah, distress beacon!
太好啦
Yeah, baby!
你这么兴奋干什么
You're excited about that?
遨游宇宙的第一法则
The first rule of space travel, kids,
务必去看看失事信标
Is always check out distress beacons.
十次有九次都是一船翘辫子的外星人
9 out of 10 times, it's a ship full of dead aliens
外加一堆东西免费拿
And a bunch of free shit!
十次能有一次是个要命的陷阱
1 out of 10 times, it's a deadly trap,
赌一把啦
But I'm ready to roll those dice.
感觉发生了很恐怖的事情啊
Seems like something terrible happened here.
赚定啦
Yep. Cha-ching.
如果发现一全是蛋的房间
Oh, yeah, if you find a room full of eggs,
别急着跑
Don't shy away from it.
拿一个摇一摇
Give one of them a shake.
抱脸虫比这艘船还值钱
Those facehuggers are worth more than this ship.
出自<异形>
- 这是干嘛  - 这样警察就会
- Uh, what's that? - This'll make the cops write it up
当成Korblock人抢劫了这船
As a looting by the Korblocks.
- 这太过分了吧  - 对嘛 警察的种族主义偏见就是深
- That's horrible. - I hear you, man. Cops are racist.
嗨 你们活着呀 感谢天感谢地
Oh, hey. You're alive. Thank god.
能帮帮我们吗
Can you help us?
我们的星球被占领了 被某种 实体
Our planet was taken over by some kind of...entity.
它吸收掉了我们族人的心智
It absorbed the minds of our people.
等我们发现已经太晚了
We didn't notice until it was too late.
被它占据的人
The people it takes over,
看上去和你的朋友
They they look like your friends,
家人 上司 没有什么两样
Your family, your leaders,
但是他们已经不再是他们自己了
But they're not themselves anymore.
他们成了它的一部分
They're part of...it.
你们怎么知道它没跟上船
Then how do you know it didn't get on the ship with you?
这俩傻子看着很淡定啊
Those two dingdongs seem pretty calm about the whole thing.
不要啊 住手
Hey, no! No, wait! Stop!
我就说
Called it.
你好啊 Rick
Hello, Rick.
好久不见
Long time no see.
联合体
Unity?
- Rick  - 外公
- Rick? - Grandpa?
哎呀
Oh, boy. Uh...
Morty和Summer是我的外孙和外孙女
These are my grandkids, Summer and Morty.
Summer Morty 这位是联合体
Summer, Morty, this is, uh, unity.
我们以前谈过一段时间恋爱
We sort of used to, uh...date.
瑞克与莫蒂
电波诚译
第二季 第三集
小联 你这儿搞得挺好的呀
Quite an operation you got going here, une.
你现在是一整个星球咯
You're a whole planet now, huh?
我们分手以后
After we broke up,
我在宇宙中漫游了一段时间
I spent some time wandering through space.
然后我发现了这里
Then I found this world
在这儿我能更好地专注于同一化的伟业
where I was better able to focus on my passion for unification.
- 就是偷别人的身体吗  - 太没礼貌了 Summer
- You mean stealing people's bodies? - Summer, rude.
你们俩孩子和联合体一边玩儿去
Why don't you two kids go run off and play with unity
我和联合体叙叙旧
While unity and I do some catching up.
等下 Rick
No, wait, Rick,
这些人不会吐我们一嘴把我们吸收掉吗
Aren't these people gonna barf into our mouths and absorb us?
你们在这里是客人
You're guests here on my planet.
可以做自己
You're free to be yourselves.
我从来都不太能让Rick失望
I've never been any good at disappointing Rick.
你再说我要吐了
Well, now I'm going to barf.
走吧 Morty
Come on, Morty.
Jerry 你在这儿干嘛呢
Jerry, what are you... what are you doing in here?
找除草机
I'm trying to find our weed whacker,
因为咱的大麻(草)老挫(音同割草)了
'cause our weeds are wack, yo.
- Rick不在 你不能进车库里来  - 不能
- But you can't go in the garage when rick's not here. - I "Can't"?
- 他会不高兴的  - 他能怎么样
- Well, he doesn't like it. - What's he gonna do?
跑去别的亲戚家白吃白住
Crash rent-free at his other family's house?
你这话什么意思
What is that supposed to mean?
你爹这么骑我们头上
Your dad gets to walk all over us
还不是因为你怕他又一走了之
Because of your abandonment issues.
妹儿咧 他这是牵着你的鼻子走
He's playing you, shorty.
好好说话 别嘻哈了
Oh, stop affecting that stupid hip-hop dialect.
你把话题转移到我说话的方式上
Stop shifting the cross hairs to my ironic urban patois
还不是因为你和你爹的关系
Just because your relationship with your father
简直是稀了个巴的烂
Is to' up from the flo' up.
什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
别管了 我们走吧
I don't know. Let's just leave.
这儿有个暗门
That is a hatch.
你爸在我的车库里装了暗门
Your father put a hatch in my garage.
又不一定是他干的
You don't know it was him.
真的 我们不该进来的
Anyway, we're not supposed to be in here.
在下面叫唤的那玩意儿也不该
Obviously, neither is whatever's gurgling down there.
"已实现世界和平" 棒
"World peace achieved." Nice.
不过你自己还要就此发报纸
Little weird to publish a paper about it
就有点奇怪了
For yourself, but hey.
然后呢
So, what's next?
等我成为一型文明以后
After I become a type-one civilization,
这颗星球会受邀进入星系联邦
This world will be invited into the galactic federation.
哦哟
Oh, goody.
我就有机会
From there, I'll have access to
接触无数的星球与种族
Countless planets and species.
一个接一个 我会将他们同化
One by one, I will unify them,
我将会成为宇宙
I will become the universe,
成为独立心智们口中
And I will be what the single-minded
所谓的神
Once called a god.
挺好的
I like that.
挺性感
Oh, that's pretty sexy.
这儿哪儿有酒喝
Hey, listen, where can we get a drink around here?
这类消遣品在这儿已经不需要了
Recreational substances were phased out here.
没有必要自我逃避
There's no need for escape from the self
世界已经融为一体
When your world is one.
联合体呀联合体 我这是和谁在说话呢
Unity, unity, who am I talking to?
我可是看着你同化了整个警察局
I watched you assimilate a whole police station
就是为了取走证物柜里的东西呢
Just to get your hands on the evidence locker.
Rick 我们相遇的时候 我还是一个年轻的群集心智
Rick, when we met, I was a young hive mind
只有一个小镇的人口
With the population of a small town.
人是会变的
People change...
尤其是我改变他们的时候
Especially when I change them.
很抱歉让你失望了
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
但我成长了
But I've grown.
我也成长了啊
Hey, listen, I've grown, too.
真的
I have!
我这不是和我的家人重聚了吗
See, I've I've reconnected with my family, right?
呵 是为了什么呢
Hm. Why's that, I wonder?
可能人变老了就是这样吧
Maybe it's part of getting old.
可能我只是怀念和一个群体在一起的日子
Maybe I just missed being with a collective.
嗯 Rick
Yes, Rick. Yes.
嗯 嗯
Oh, yeah. Yes. Yes.
停 等下
Wait, wait. Stop. Hold it.
光这样不行
Not like this.
来一悬挂式滑翔机
We need a hang glider
一套开档的山姆大叔衣服
And a crotchless uncle sam costume,
然后你这儿最大的体育场
And I want the entire field of your largest stadium
场地上塞满裸体的红发美女
Covered end to end with naked redheads,
看台上面再挤满
And I want the stands packed
所有远看着像我爸爸的人
With every man that remotely resembles my father.
看看他们 太协调了
Man, look at them go. So coordinated.
你怎么了
What's your problem?
他们给你雕了一个总统山
They're making you into a mount rushmore.
还有汉堡吃
They made burgers!
Morty你睁大眼看看
Morty, open your eyes.
"他们"已经不在了
There is no "They."
这些可怜人的身体被利用了
These poor people's bodies are being used.
这一整个星球都是人偶罢了
They're a planet of puppets.
你说什么我能听到的
I can hear you.
但是我觉得这里的人都觉得没关系啊
Well, it seems like everybody here's cool with it.
除了那些红发美女
Except for all those redheads.
看上去急着去什么地方呢
They seem like they're in a hurry to be somewhere else.
Summer要气球吗
Balloon, Summer?
Morty呢
Balloon, Morty?
我们才不要你的破气球
No, we don't want your dumb balloons, okay?
我们现在很无聊 带我们去找Rick
We're bored. Take us back to Rick.
现在不太合适
Now's not a good time.
爽
Oh, yeah!
来吧宝贝儿
I want yooooooou!
儿呀 上啊
Go, son, go!
Go, son, go! Go, son, go!
哎哟哟 真是不得了
Oh, real nice. Real nice.
我完全没发现 怎么做到的
How does a man do this without me noticing?
我爸嘛 你也知道
Oh, you know my dad
他做事要是用点心
Once he puts his mind to something.
你还表扬他的成果
You're spinning this to his credit?
我要下去
I'm going down there.
- Jerry - Beth 这是我家房子
- Jerry - Beth, this is my house,
所以这是我的车库 我的暗门
Which makes this my garage, my secret hatch,
我的地下密室 以及我的无脸秘怪
My hidden subterranean lair, and my faceless gargler.
你现在是要继续怨我
Now, are you gonna keep hating this playa
还是遂了窝的西
Or are you gonna jack my steez?
你这已经是在胡编乱造瞎胡说了
Okay, you're just making stuff up now.
我个天
Ugh. Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
Rick 今天这次真是棒呢
Oh, Rick. That was so bad.
"今天这次"是什么意思
What's this "Was" Stuff?
我就是补充点水分
I just need to hydrate,
完了接着来
Then we're doing that again.
- 该死  - 如果是来侵略的
- Oh, damn. - Listen, if this is an invasion,
我也做不了啥
I got to sit this one out,
但是我会回来和幸存者做爱的
But I'll be back to have sex with the survivors.
是邻近的群集心智的种族
It's a neighboring hive-mind species,
Beta Seven是在致敬<星际迷航>中的种族Borg
贝塔七
Beta seven.
我们星球之间保持着实用的联盟关系
Our planets maintain a practical alliance
交换关键资源
For exchange of vital resources,
友善点
So be nice.
联合体
Unity,
我来得不是时候吗
Is it a bad time?
当前的所有生命都被同化了吗
Are all present life forms assimilated?
贝塔七 这是我的独立心智朋友 Rick
Beta seven, this is my single-minded friend
他来自地球
From earth, Rick.
Rick Sanchez
Rick Sanchez.
Unity跟我提到过你
Unity has spoken of you.
都是坏话吧 哈哈
All bad, I hope. Ha ha!
天呐你这动静
Oh, jesus christ.
七号 如果你对我的盟友有意见
Beta seven, if my allies are a problem for you,
那我们的联盟也不能继续了
Perhaps our alliance is, as well.
我们的联盟是互利的
Our alliance is beneficial.
贝塔七表示出的关心
When beta seven expresses concern,
只是因为
It it's only be-because
我的老天 这是零号元素的粉末
Oh, snap! Powdered neutronium?
安非他粒子
Amphetetron?
有了这些东西 你知道我能做出什么吗
You know I can make with this stuff?
Rick 我不能这样
Oh, Rick, I I shouldn't.
别啊 我又不是每天都能来找你
Come on. It's not every day that I'm in town.
想想我们曾经的美好时光
It's it's for old time's sake.
那 好吧 管他呢
Uh...okay, what the hell.
我们可以纯化树脂 做迷幻粉
We can purify the resin and make fractal dust.
我是想做光速马天尼的
Oh, I was thinking velocitinis, but
怎么 Rick老了 不能和整个星球的人狂欢了吗
Aw, old man Rick can't party with a whole planet?
你们能做的 我都能做哟 还不止呢
I can do whatever you do and more, baby.
我觉得那个贝塔七
You know, I think beta seven over there
不只是想和保持"实用"的联盟关系而已
Is hoping your alliance can be more than practical.
讨厌
Stop.
怪不得电费贵到离谱
Well, this explains the $6,000 electric bill.
天呐
Whoa!
行 真可以
Well, nice. Real nice.
在我房子下面关外星人
Alien prisoners under the house.
真行
Real nice.
真真的好
Nice. Reeeeeeeeeeeeeal
给老娘闭嘴
God damn it, stop.
醒醒吧诸位 你们得反抗
Wake up, people! You have to fight it!
你们被邪物施咒了
You're under the spell of an evil monster!
- 你说什么我能听到的 - 这句话你就接着说吧
- I can hear you. - Yeah, so you keep saying.
- Summer  - 醒醒吧
- Summer! - Wake up!
你至少还残存着一点自我的意识吧
You have to have some individuality left in there!
Summer 你为什么不喜欢我
Why do you hate me, Summer?
我没跟你说话
I'm not talking to you.
我跟他说话的人是这位 Steven Phillips
I'm talking to... Steven Phillips.
Steven 重获自由吧
Steven, set yourself free.
Summer 在我占领这个星球之前
Summer, before I took over this planet,
这个人是登记在案的性侵犯者
This man was a registered sex offender.
那又怎么样 至少那是他自己
Yeah? Well, so what? At least he was himself.
这女的原先是个几近自杀的瘾君子
This woman was a drug addict on the verge of suicide.
现在她是海洋生物学家
Now she's a marine biologist.
听着 我觉得我姐姐的意思不是说
Listen, Unity, I don't think my sister's trying to say
没有你干预的生命就是完美的
That life would be perfect without you.
她的意思是 这样的生命
I think she's just saying that life would be,
才是生命的样子
You know, life.
生命在这里因为我的转化宛若天堂
I have transformed life here into a paradise.
站街女成了科学家
Prostitutes are now scientists.
流浪汉变"则学家"
The homeless are now "Phisosophers."
"则学家"吗 真棒
Oh. Oh. "Ph-phisosophers"? Nice.
- 则学 择靴  - 天呐
- Philopol... phiphophopher... - Oh, my god.
谁教会你说的话 你这骗走外公的婊子
Where did you learn to talk, you grandpa-stealing slut?
我感觉
I'm feeling...
天呐 我来扶你们
Oh, man, let me help all of you guys up.
我没事
I'm fine.
你知道我爱你哪一点吗 Rick
Do you know what I love about you, Rick?
你是我遇到的唯一一个有长远眼光的
You're the only single mind I've met
独立心智生物
that really sees the big picture.
你没看走眼
You got that right.
宝贝 听着
But, baby, listen
你 你是要占领无数星球甚至星系的人
Y-you're talking about taking over planets and galaxies.
你一定 一定要记住
You got to got to just remember
有时候要放松随意 别老紧绷着
to let go sometimes, you know?
我可以很随意啊 看我的
I can let go. Hey, look.
你看到河对岸那个小镇了吗
You see that town across the river?
看着
Watch this.
- 天呐  - 哈哈
- Whoa! - Ha ha! Whoo!
我不是这个意思
Whoa! That's not what I meant!
没事的 没事
It's okay. It's okay.
我已经疏散了小镇上的人 你看
I evacuated. I evacuated the town. Look.
我们在这里 我们没事
Hey! We're right here. We're fine.
太赞了
Oh, that was awesome.
我的孙子孙女没在那个镇子吧
My my grandkids weren't in that town, right?
他 他们还活着吧
A-are my grandkids alive?
我 我的酒喝完了
M-my drink is empty.
- 怎么回事啊联合体  - 联合体是谁
- Unity, what's happening? - Who's Unity?
你们两个的脚真好看 我能拍个照吗
You kids have nice feet. Mind if I take a picture?
真恶心 不要
Gross. No.
我觉得你的愿望要成真了 Summer
I think you're getting what you wanted, Summer.
联合体好像出了什么问题
Something's happening to Unity.
你们还记得自己是谁吗
Do all of you remember who you are?
记得 我叫Ron Benson
Yeah, uh, my name is Ron Benson.
我是个电子工程师 有两个孩子
I'm an electrical engineer, father of two,
看见我的两个同心双圆平乳环 你就能知道
And, as you can see from my flat, concentric nipple rings,
我是这个星球上最高贵的种族
I'm a member of this planet's top race!
好吧
Okay, that's good.
就是别再想你说的后半截
Uh, don't focus too much on the last part, but
我叫Daryl Jefferson 是个地产商
I'm Daryl Jefferson. I'm a landscaper.
我死也不同意
And I'll be damned if
那胸上穿洞的贱人是优等种族
That ripple-nipple bitch's race is superior!
锥子胸人才是世界的统治者
The cone-nipple people will rule this world!
闭嘴吧 你这胸上长角的傻逼
You shut your mouth, you dirty knife-nipple bastards.
你说我什么
What'd you say to me,
你这个奶头似靶心的废物
You target-chest piece of shit.
种族战争
Race war!
你们何必打架呢
Why are you fighting?!
你们看不出大家都是一样的吗
Can't you see you're all the same?
Summer
Oh, Summer.
第一次见识种族战争吧你
First race war, huh?
Summer你真棒 挑起了种族战争
Way to go, Summer. You started a race war.
不是我引起的 他们才是种族主义者
I didn't start it! They're the racists.
我 我只是点燃了导火索
I... I merely empowered them
让他们追寻本来就扭曲的梦想
to follow their apparently misguided dreams.
多谢你有心说明
Okay, thanks for clarifying.
这下我的墓碑上就能写清楚了
I'll have a super-accurate headstone now.
你们两个是什么种族
Hey, wait what race are you guys?
都不是 你看
We're neither. S-see?
听我说
Yeah, take my word for it.
我们就是普普通通的乳头
We just have regular nipples.
这两个怪物没有种族
Hey, these two freaks have no race!
没有哪里比得上家
Oh, there's no place like home.
<绿野仙踪> 中桃乐西说出这句话以后便回到了家
没有哪里比得上家 你还记得吗Summer
There's no place like home. Remember, Summer?
- 里边儿有桃乐西和小矮人的电影  - 我记得
- From Dorothy and the tiny people movie? - Yes, yes.
- 都是小不点  - 桃乐西 带我们走吧
- All the tiny people. - Dorothy, take us away.
Summer Morty 你们好啊
Hello, Summer. Hello, Morty.
- 你们现在安全了  - 你是联合体吗
- It's okay. You're safe now. - Unity?
- 是的  - 实在抱歉
- Yes. - Oh, Unity, I am so sorry.
我不知道自由意味着人们会做这种蠢事
I didn't know freedom meant people doing stuff that sucks.
我以为自由
I was thinking more of
就是能自己选自己手机的运营商
A choose your own cellphone-carrier thing.
你并没有做错什么
Oh, Summer, you did nothing wrong.
我和你外公玩得有点过
I'm having fun with your grandpa.
有点失控了
Lost a little control.
貌似现在不适合开着飞行器
Probably shouldn't be piloting a hovercopter,
管理着二十万所儿科医院
Nor should I be running 200,000 pediatric hospitals
还有一千两百万个油炸锅
And 12 million deep fryers,
但是这个星球的事情
But hey, it's not like this planet
又不能撒手不管了
Can take its business elsewhere.
我们是不是该半路停一下
Um, should we maybe stop somewhere
你先喝点咖啡缓缓神
And get you a coffee?
要不往你脸上浇点冷水什么的 或者
Maybe splash a little water on your face, or...
哦不不 如果我想要清醒的话
No, no, if I wanted to be sober,
我一开始就不会喝醉了
I wouldn't have gotten drunk.
天呐 我等不及了
Oh, man. I cannot wait
我迫不及待想听听他怎么解释
I cannot wait to hear Rick explain his way around this.
他必须走
He is gone.
Jerry 求你别这样好吗
Jerry, stop, please, okay?
我们都不应该来这里的
We weren't even supposed to be down here.
我们只要找他当面对峙
If we confront him about this
哎哟 我真喜欢你这样
Oh, my god! I love this.
你这样百般为他辩解
I love that this is how far you will go for him.
你就想上楼切你的胡萝卜
You want to go upstairs and cut carrots
然后看你的肥皂剧
And watch a lifetime original
就在这[哔]关了外星人的地牢上面
Above a [bleep] alien dungeon!
你和你爸的关系很病态
Your relationship with your father is psychotic.
你听听你这添油加醋的说
Oh, listen to you relish the idea
说到底就是我的天才老爸是个坏人
that my genius father is a bad person.
先把你的好胜心放一边
Step out of your ego for a second
看看这东西 这是个怪物
And look at this thing it's a monster.
恐怕他把这怪物锁起来
He might have it chained up
是为了防止它把我们的星球吃掉吧
So that it doesn't eat the planet!
是啊 你爸就是这么为他人着想
Right, because your father's such an altruist?
我有次看到他连"人类"这个词都忘了怎么说
I once saw him briefly forget the word for "Humans".
他说不定是为了收集这个生物的器官
He's probably harvesting this creature's organs.
他说不定是要抢着先治愈这东西的太空艾滋病
He's probably racing to cure its space aids.
- 他要吃了它  - 他在保护它
- He's going to eat it! - He's protecting it!
- 闭嘴  - 闭嘴
- Shut up! - Shut up!
哎呦
Whoa!
这地方简直一团糟
Unity, this place is a mess.
没关系
Oh, it's cool.
我作为保洁员的那一部分周五就会过来
The part of me that's the cleaning lady is coming on Friday.
天呐 一个小时之后
Oh, my god. I have a meeting
我还要在银河联邦开会
At the galactic federation in an hour.
我到不了了
Oh, I'll never make it.
那就推到下周吧
Ah, I'll push it to next week.
Unity 你能把Rick叫到这里吗
Unity, could you get Rick out here, please?
他有事脱不开身 他正在
He's unavailable. He's...
正在和你做爱 我们明白 真恶心
Having sex with you. We get it. Gross.
现在就让他出来
Get him out here now.
我觉得他不会想来的
I don't think he wants to be
- 外公  - Rick
- Grandpa Rick! - Rick! Rick!
我要告诉爸妈
I'm gonna tell mom and dad about the gagoo
你在车库锁了个Gagoo
You have locked up under the garage!
你们到底要闹哪样
What the hell is your problem?
我们要回家 立刻马上
Grandpa, we need to go home, now.
天 随便你
Fine. Sheesh.
拜拜
See you.
Rick 我们一起走啊
Uh, Rick, I think we should all go.
玩你们自己的去 孩子们 我这儿忙着呢
Tend to your garden, kids. I'm kind of doing a thing here.
喔耶
Whoo!
外公 你不走我们也不走
Grandpa Rick, we're not leaving without you.
我的天 孩子们 我懂了
Oh, my god, you guys. I get it.
你们是怕强大的坏联合体
You're afraid the big, bad hive mind
抢走你们的外公
Is gonna steal your grandpa away.
才怪呢 我现在觉得联合体很伟大
Actually, no. I think Unity's great
是你在带坏它
And you're a horrible influence on it.
- 啥  - Rick 你们的关系很不健康
- What?  - This isn't healthy, Rick.
你知道吗 你给这儿带来的
You know, you're you're really up to no good around here
都是负面影响 不是吗
a-at this place, you know?
你和联合体就像
You and Unity are like
紧身裤和中短靴
Like leggings and mid-calf boots.
自以为很相配
You think you're great together,
但其实互暴其短
But you're just bringing out the worst in each other.
天哪 Summer 挺会说的哈
Oh, gee. Boy, Summer. Well put.
不如我们看看联合体怎么想
Uh, why don't we see what Unity thinks?
联合体
Unity?
我只是想寻点乐子
I'm just taking a little break from stuff.
你懂吗 我需要放松
You know? I need to relax.
哎呀 这是什么新闻
Oh, hey, w-what's this on the news, guys?
把声音调大点
L-l-let me turn it up.
今日新闻
In the news today,
实际情况没有看上去那么糟
This looks a lot worse than it is.
只是寻寻乐子 无伤大雅
We're really just having a good time.
- Karen  - 谢谢 Todd
- Karen?  - Thanks, Todd.
下则新闻 你到底是忧心的孙辈
Up next, are you a concerned grandchild
还是扫兴鬼
Or just a buzzkill?
我们马上告诉你如何获得正确答案
We'll tell you how you can know for sure.
你们少数得服从多数了吧
I think you two are a little outnumbered.
好吧 那如果是为了我呢
Okay, well, what if you did it for me?
依你孙子女的 一起回去
What if you came with us as a favor to us
因为你爱我们
Because you love us?
啥咧 傻哭 拜拜
What? Dumb. Bye.
Rick Summer她只是
But Rick, Summer's just
她只是个多愁善感的缺爱
Summer's just a hyper-emotional, needy little
什么来着
What's the word I'm looking for here?
呃 人类
Uh...human.
家族遗传没办法
It runs in the family.
我可以容忍但我懒得伺候
I can tolerate it, but I can't give a crap about it.
慢走不送
Take a hike.
自求多福吧 联合体
Take care of yourself, Unity.
我不想听说教 请答是或否
I'm not looking for judgment, just a yes or no
你能把长颈鹿同化吗
Can you assimilate a giraffe?
- 你简直不可理喻  - 你才是
- You're the worst!  - No, you're the worst!
你根本不给我们的家庭一点支持
You don't support this family!
- 你认为支持你  - 你脑子里只能想到自己
- You think supporting the family  - All you care about is yourself!
- 就是支持这个家庭  - 我们两个孩子
- Is about supporting you emotionally...  - you've got two children...
- 但谁能受得了你  - 被你的神经病老爹
- but you're unsupportable.  - being dragged across the cosmos
你根本是个无底洞
because it's never enough,
- Jerry  - 拖到满宇宙去溜
- Jerry!  - ...by your dangerously ill father!
还要我忍气吞声
And you force me to watch it
就因为你太害怕失去他
happen because you'd rather lose them and lose me...
因为你根本不懂
And you don't even know what it's
- 害怕失去是什么感觉  - 宁愿失去我和孩子们
- like to be afraid of losing anything  - ...than lose him!
因为你只懂依赖
Because you cling and you cling.
为什么 因为幼稚的是你 Beth
And why? Because you're the child, Beth!
不是我 是你
You, not me! You!
我的天啊
Oh, my god. Aah!
初次见面 你们好
Um, first of all, hello.
哟 我是Korblock人 叫Blim Blam
Uh, my name is blim blam the korblok.
其次 我就直说了吧
Second of all, cards on the table,
我是个爱吃婴儿的怪物
I'm a murderer that eats babies,
我就是来地球吃婴儿的
And I came to this planet to eat babies.
除此之外 我还携带一种传染性极强的疾病
However, I am also carrying a highly infectious disease
按你们的叫法算是 太空艾滋
That I suppose you could call "Space aids" As you put it.
而Rick把我锁在这里
And rick did chain me up
的确是为了寻求治愈的疗法
So that he could attempt to cure it.
然而
At the same time,
他治疗我
Rick's motivation to cure my disease
不是为了救我 或救任何人
Was not to save my life or anyone else's,
而是为了申请专利 大赚一笔
But to patent and sell the cure for billions of blemflarcks.
但你们知道我为何
But you know the reason why
要挣脱掉镣铐的吗
I ripped my chains out of the wall?
你们知道为何我决定再不返回这个星球吗
And do you know why i'm never coming back to this planet?
因为你们俩简直[哔]不可理喻
Because the two of you are the [bleep] worst!
你们厌恶对方 更厌恶自己
You both hate yourselves and each other.
还把这一切怪到Rick身上
And the idea that it has anything to do with rick
简直可笑
Is laughable.
我都憋不住了 可惜我没笑这功能
I'd laugh, but I'm biologically incapable.
因为我他妈是个外星人
That's how alien I am.
但外星人如我 听到你俩在那里逼逼叨
And even I'm sitting here listening to the two of you
都[哔]的受不了了
And being like, "What the [bleep]"
好了 祝你们俩这烂婚百年好合
So good luck with your shitty marriage,
请转告Rick 我很同情他摊上你们这种人
And tell rick I'm sorry he has to deal with either of you.
Blim Blam 闪人
Blim blam out.
这玩意儿我要了
You know what? I'm taking this.
怎么开不了
How do you.. what is this?
这是慢速模式吗
Uh, is there a slow setting?
这门 太赞
Best door ever.
我想看他们哭 但是要幸福的泪水
Okay, okay. Now make them cry, but happy crying.
让他们取笑金发的那个
Now make them all make fun of the blonde one.
让他们到桌上去弄
Now make them all do it on the table.
难以置信 你竟为我拍了一部电视剧
I can't believe you created a whole show for me.
现在砍了它
Now cancel it.
哈哈 续订 续订
Okay, now put it back on.
好吧 我玩腻了
All right, I'm bored.
Rick 你要不联系一下
Rick, is there a way for you
Summer和Morty
To call Summer and Morty?
- 我挺歉意的 他们  - 切 让他们玩蛋去
- I feel bad that they..  - Pbht. screw those guys.
我去去就回
Ugh. I'll be right back.
别在小混蛋们身上浪费精力 联合体
Don't waste your brain on those weirdos, Unity.
他们和你占据的
They're no different from any of
那些行尸走肉没多大区别
the aimless chumps that you occupy.
只是因为你强大
They just put you at the
他们才把你奉为世界的中心
center of their lives because you're powerful.
但因为是他们把你捧上去的
And then because they put you there,
他们又想限制你
They want you to be less powerful.
休想得逞 对吧
Never gonna happen though, right?
对
Never.
休想得逞 待会儿见
Never. Back in a flash.
有史以来最爽的周末 Rick
Best weekend ever, Rick.
我同意 Rick 让我们再接再厉
I agree, Rick. Let's see how long we can go.
小联 你还有
Hey, Une. You got any more
原谅我 Rick 我只能留下字条
Rick, forgive me for doing this in notes.
我没有和你当面告别的勇气
I'm not strong enough to do it in persons.
我现在懂了 你吸引我的地方
I realize now that I'm attracted to you
正是我不能和你在一起的原因
For the same reason I can't be with you.
你无法改变
You can't change.
这不是坏事
And I have no problem with that,
但对我来说 却是无法迈过的一道坎
But it clearly means I have a problem with myself.
我知道完美的我并不存在
I'm sure there's no perfect version of me
我知道我会同化一个接一个的种族
I'm sure I'll just unify species after species
却永远无法真正的完美
And never really be complete.
但我知道我们的结局
But I know how it goes with us.
我会失去自我 成为你的一部分
I lose who I am and become part of you.
最为奇怪的就在于此
Because in a strange way,
明明是我的专长 你毫不费力便胜过了我
You're better at what I do without even trying.
永远独属于你的
Yours, and nobody else's,
联合体
Unity.
顺带一提 我不知道被同化前
P.S., I don't know where those coal miners were
那些煤工们去过什么地方
Before they were assimilated.
你最好去体检一下
You might want to get checked.
嘿
Hey.
爸爸
Dad.
Jerry和我
I, um Jerry and I
在找我们的除草机时
Were looking for our weed whacker
发现了你的地下密室
And found your subterranean lair
和你的外星囚犯
And your alien prisoner,
他跑了
And he got away.
我知道我听上去像妈妈
And I know I sound like mom,
但我不能因为害怕失去你的恐惧
But I can't sacrifice this whole family's safety
而牺牲整个家庭的安全
Just because I'm afraid you'll leave again,
所以 不要再囚禁外星人了
So no more alien prisoners
也不要再在地下动土了
And no more subterranean excavation
至少预先和我们商议一下
Without consulting us.
- 行  - 行
- Okay.  - Okay?
你的"行"就是丢下一句话就把自己传送走
"Okay" Like you're gonna quietly teleport somewhere
- 永不回来吗  - 不 这是你的房子
- And never come back?  - No. It's your house.
外公 你和联合体怎么了
Grandpa Rick, what happened with Unity?
谁 联合体啊
Who? Oh, Unity. Yeah, well...
老实说 它是个把自己的兴盛
I mean, honestly, we're talking about an entity
建立在奴役之上的存在 不是吗
That thrives on enslavement, you know?
这可不好 虽然有趣 但谁消受得起
It's not cool. Fun's fun, but who needs it?
我去车库了
I'll be in the garage.
Chaos Chaos
<Do You Feel It>
联合体 联合体
Unity! Unity!
联合体
Unity!
- 请问需要什么帮助  - 我要和联合体谈谈
- How can I assist you?  - I want to talk to Unity,
贝塔七 我知道它在这里
Beta seven, I know it's in there.
你已被认定为敌对单位
You're classified as a hostile entity,
联合体不想跟你谈
and Unity doesn't want to talk to you.
我知道你的把戏 贝塔七号
I know your game, beta seven.
你这种的我见多了
I've met a billion of you,
你这个召之即来挥之即去的备胎
You little on-deck, in-the-wings shoulder to cry on!
你已被认定为敌对单位
You are classified as a hostile entity.
哎哟 你他妈还得瑟了是吧
Oh, you're just loving this, mother
别想得太美了
This isn't gonna shake out like you think, pal.
联合体不可能喜欢其他的群集心智
Unity's not into other hive minds.
它不过是想利用你 同化你
It's gonna suck you in and use you up,
再等一个月
And a month from now,
你就得带着红色假发
I'm gonna be making out with all of you
跟我亲热了
In a bunch of red wigs!
联合体 联合体
Unity! Unity!
联合体 我知道你能听到 快出来
Unity, I know you can hear me. Get out here.
武器系统已开启
Weapons systems engaged.
就你这瘪三还武器系统
Oh, in your dreams you have weapon systems.
Rick 你不是说我们是出来看电影的吗
Ugh, Rick, you said we were going to a movie.
本来就是 Morty
We are, Morty.
好吧 瘪塔七号
All right, Beta shit seven,
算你走运 小婊子
You just got saved by the bell, bitch!
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组